[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Along with the minerals extracted from nutrients, the human body also produces minerals of its own, essential for maintaining it in good condition.", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In The Godfather, the snooty movie director who refused to give a part to a friend of the Corleone family found the head of his prized horse in his bed. What was the value of the horse?", "correct_answer": "700,000 dollars", "incorrect_answers": ["100,000 dollars", "200,000 dollars", "70,000 dollars"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "None of the major players in Rocky Horror  appeared in any of the 100 Top films.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This disease had 7 pandemics and is still causing epidemics.", "correct_answer": "Cholera", "incorrect_answers": ["Plague", "Typhus", "Influenza"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the title character in the movie Young Frankenstein?", "correct_answer": "Gene Wilder", "incorrect_answers": ["Gene Hackman", "Peter Boyle", "Kenneth Mars"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these leaders was NOT known as Generalissimo?", "correct_answer": "Adolf Hitler", "incorrect_answers": ["Augusto Pinochet", "Kim Il-sung", "Chiang Kai-shek"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who said the words There\u2019s your gawd-damned dinner!! ?", "correct_answer": "Nick Nolte in 48 Hours", "incorrect_answers": ["Kevin Spacey in Seven", "Mel Brooks in To Be Or Not To Be", "Danny Devito in Ruthless People"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which country was the 2007 film Ghost Rider mostly filmed?", "correct_answer": "Australia", "incorrect_answers": ["New Zealand", "USA", "Britain"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If the world were a village of 100 people, how many would be white?", "correct_answer": "18", "incorrect_answers": ["37", "32", "25"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In The Wizard of Oz movie, Scarecrow states which very important mathematical theorem?", "correct_answer": "The Law of Pythagoras", "incorrect_answers": ["Euclids Fifth Postulate", "Eulers Theorem", "Newtons Axiom"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The prefix neuro, which in Greek means sinew or string, is related to the nervous system.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The main function of this organ of respiration is to transport oxygen from the atmosphere into the bloodstream.", "correct_answer": "lung", "incorrect_answers": ["stomach", "diaphragm", "trachea"]}]